http://www.bloodshotrecords.com/privacy-policy

Jump to navigation
Thank you for your ongoing support and patience with our small operation this year. Our warehouse is operating with shortened hours and thoughtful hygienic and social distancing protocol. Please allow a couple extra days for orders to ship.Be kind, wash your hands, and thank your postal workers.
Bloodshot Radio
Search form
Search
Log in
About Us
Contact
Privacy Policy
Website Visitors
Like most website operators, Bloodshot Records collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Bloodshot Records’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Bloodshot Records’ visitors use its website.
Bloodshot Records also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users. Bloodshot Records only discloses logged in user IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below.One of your rights under law is that you must be informed when your personal data is processed (collected, used, stored) by any organization. You also have the right to know the details and purpose of that processing.
Some of the services offered on our website require the processing of your personal data. In such cases, links are available directing you to the specific information about the processing contained in the relevant data protection notices.
Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information
Certain visitors to Bloodshot Records’s websites choose to interact with Bloodshot Records in ways that require Bloodshot Records to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Bloodshot Records gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. Those who engage in transactions with Bloodshot Records are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, Bloodshot Records collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with Bloodshot Records. Bloodshot Records does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.
Aggregated Statistics
Bloodshot Records may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. Bloodshot Records may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, Bloodshot Records does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.
Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information
Bloodshot Records discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on Bloodshot Records’ behalf or to provide services available at Bloodshot Records’s websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using Bloodshot Records’s websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. Bloodshot Records will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, Bloodshot Records discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when Bloodshot Records believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Bloodshot Records, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of an Bloodshot Records website and have supplied your email address, Bloodshot Records may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with Bloodshot Records and our products. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. Bloodshot Records takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.
Bloodshot Records collects your personal information only to the extent necessary to fulfil a precise purpose related to our tasks as an institution (which are laid down in Regulation 45/2001). We do not reuse the information for another purpose that is different to the one stated. We put in place measures to guarantee that your data are kept up-to-date and processed securely. We will never divulge your personal data for direct marketing purposes. You have the right to access your personal information, to have it corrected and the right to recourse at any time if you believe your data protection rights have been breached. We do not keep your personal information for longer than necessary for the purposes for which we collected it. However, we may keep your information for a longer period for historical, statistical or scientific purposes with the appropriate safeguards in place.You are entitled to access the personal data the Bloodshot Records holds about you and to have them rectified where necessary. In certain cases, you also have the right to have your data blocked or erased or to object to their processing. For more information, please see Articles 13 to 19 of the GDPR Regulation.
To exercise any of these rights, please contact us at bshq[at]bloodshotrecords.com. We will reply within one week. Please note that in some cases restrictions under Article 20 of the Regulation may apply.
Cookies
A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Bloodshot Records uses cookies to help Bloodshot Records identify and track visitors, their usage of Bloodshot Records website, and their website access preferences. Bloodshot Records visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Bloodshot Records’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of Bloodshot Records’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies. Cookies are also typically used to provide a more personalised experience for a user for example, when an online service remembers your user profile without you having to login. When you visit our website, we may collect some data on your browsing experience such as your IP address, the Bloodshot page you visited, when you visited and the website page you were redirected from. This information is used to gather aggregated and anonymous statistics with a view to improving our services and to enhance your user experience. When you visit the Bloodshot website, we will keep the browser history of your visit for a maximum of 13 months. This information will then be deleted.
Links to other websites
This privacy policy does not cover links within this site to other websites. We encourage you to read the privacy policies on any website you visit.
Business Transfers
If Bloodshot Records, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, or in the unlikely event that Bloodshot Records goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of Bloodshot Records may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.The Bloodshot Records website is entirely SSL protected. SSL provides a secure connection between your site and the end user's web browser that's authenticated and encrypted with an SSL Certificate. This makes it less likely (but not entirely impossible) that private data will be intercepted by a malicious third-party and is in line with the "Privacy by Design" aspect of the GDPR Regulation.
Social Media
We use social media to present our work through widely used and contemporary channels. Our use of social media is highlighted on this website. For instance, you can watch Bloodshot videos, which we upload to our YouTube page and follow links from our website to Twitter, Facebook, and Instagram. Cookies are not set by our display of social media buttons to connect to those services when our website pages are loaded on your computer (or other devices) or from components from those services embedded in our web pages. Each social media channel has their own policy on the way they process your personal data when you access their sites. For example, if you choose to watch one of our videos on YouTube, you will be asked for explicit consent to accept YouTube cookies; if you look at our Twitter activity on Twitter, you will be asked for explicit consent to accept Twitter cookies; the same applies for Facebook and Instagram or any other social media service on which official Bloodshot content appears.
If you have any concerns or questions about their use of your personal data, you should read their privacy policies carefully before using them.
Google Analytics
Bloodshot Records uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. ("Google"). Google Analytics uses cookies to help Bloodshot analyze how visitors use this site. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the website (including your IP address) will be transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the United States.
This site has activated IP anonymization, which means Google will truncate/anonymize the last octet of a visitor’s IP address. Only in exceptional cases will the full IP address be sent to and shortened by Google servers in the USA.
On behalf of Bloodshot, Google will use this information for the purpose of evaluating your use of the website, compiling reports on website activity for website operators, and providing other services relating to website activity and internet usage to the website provider. Google will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google.
You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser.
Opting out
By default, the browsing experience of website visitors is tracked by Google Analytics in order to produce anonymized statistics.
You can prevent Google’s collection and use of data (cookies and IP address) by downloading and installing the Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on. Please note that on this website, Google Analytics code is supplemented by “gat._anonymizeIp();” to ensure an anonymized collection of IP addresses (so called IP-masking).
Do Not Track Preferences
Do not track is a function that allows visitors to opt out from being tracked by websites for any purpose including the use of analytics services, advertising networks and social platforms. Do not track options are available in a number of browsers including:
Firefox
Chrome
Safari
Opera
If you enable do not track in your web browser, Google Analytics will respect your choice, and you will not be tracked. This is in addition to you opting-out of the aggregation and analysis of data for our website statistics.
If you have disabled all cookies from your browser, we will still collect some general data about your browsing (e.g. a record of a visitor to our website) but they will be less accurate and your visit will not be tracked.
Notice of Breach
If a security breach causes an unauthorized intrusion into our system that materially affects you or your personal data, Bloodshot Records will notify you as soon as possible (within 72 hours of discovery) and follow up with a notice of any action(s) taken in response.
Privacy Policy Changes
Although most changes are likely to be minor, Bloodshot Records may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Bloodshot Records’s sole discretion. Bloodshot Records encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
Questions?
If you have any questions about this privacy policy, please contact us at bshq[at]bloodshotrecords.com
"There comes a time when every man feels the urge to spit on his hands, hoist the black flag, and start slitting throats." — H.L. Mencken
bshq@bloodshotrecords.com | 3039 W. Irving Park Rd. Chicago, IL 60618 | 773-604-5300 | © 2014-2020 Bloodshot Records
